felixfilms.net 2018-09-02

# PRIVACY

At http://www.feflixfilms.net, the privacy of our visitors is very important to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by http://www.felixfilms.net and how it is used. 

**Log file**

Like many other Web sites, http://www.felixfilms.net uses log files. Information in log files includes internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date / time stamp, referring / exiting pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, manage sites, track user movements around the location, and gather demographic information. The IP address, and other information is not related to personal information. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

http://www.felixfilms.net does not use cookies to store information about visitor preferences, record certain user information on any page the user accesses or visits, adjust the content of web pages based on the type of visitor's browser or other information that sends visitors through their browser. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

. :: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads at http://www.felixfilms.net. 

. :: Google using the DART cookie makes it possible to display ads to users based on their visit to http://www.felixfilms.net and other sites on the Internet. 

. :: Users can cancel the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google network ad and content privacy policy at the following URL -http: //www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .... 

**Google Adsense**

Third-party ad servers or ad networks using ad technology and links that appear on http://www.felixfilms.net send directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) can also be used by third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

http://www.felixfilms.net has no access to or control over cookies used by third party advertisers. 

You should consult the privacy policies of each of the third party ad servers for more detailed information about their practices and to get instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. http://www.felixfilms.net's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, other advertisers or websites. 

If you want to disable cookies, you can do so through individual browser options. More information about management cookies with certain web browsers can be found on the respective browser's website.
